nittygriddy.com 2011-03-13

# Terms & Privacy and Other Legal Jargon | nittyGriddy

This privacy policy applies to the use of http://nittyGriddy.com

**General**

Welcome to **nitty** **Griddy** and thank you for visiting my blog! I hope you will enjoy viewing my site with as much pleasure as I enjoy presenting it to you.

I highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout my site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using nittygriddy.com.

**Agreement Regarding Use of this Website**

I invite you to view and comment on this blog. Your use of the blog will signify your agreement to abide by our guidelines stated below.

By submitting or posting content or comments to this site, (at this time it is simply a blog but I may decide to expand the services/offerings at a later date) you grant nittygriddy.com and its owners, principals, affiliates, subsidiaries and licensees the right to use, reproduce, display, perform, adapt, modify, distribute, have distributed, and promote such content and comments in any form, anywhere and for any purpose; and you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to such content and comments and that public posting and use of your content and comments by nittygriddy.com and its owners, principals, affiliates, subsidiaries and licensees will not infringe or violate the rights of any third party.

_*See last paragraph of this document._

**Privacy**

This website is the property of nittyGriddy.com (Ingrid Abboud)

  * I can be reached via e-mail through the [Contact](http://nittygriddy.com/email-me/) ([Em@il Me](http://nittygriddy.com/email-me/ "Em@il Me")) page. 
  * For each visitor to my Web page, my Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.
  * I collect information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.
  * With respect to Ad Servers (a service I may decide to include in the future): At this time, please visit the Google Adsense website for more information on this service and consult their privacy policies. 

**Log Files**

This website **may** utilize industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to my website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. **This information does not identify individual users;** it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

**Registration and Use of Personal Information**

Registration **may** be required in order to use or access this website – although at this present time it isn’t.

**Security**

I follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to me. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore , as is the case with any organization, I am not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

**Links to Other Websites**

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by nittygriddy.com. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; nittygriddy.com is not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than its own. Consequently, I strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit in general regardless of whether or not they are linked to by nittygriddy.com

**Disclaimer**

Please note that opinions expressed herein are solely those of nittygriddy.com. nittygriddy.com does not make any representations or warranties as to the accuracy, timeliness, suitability, completeness, or relevance of any information prepared by any unaffiliated third party, whether linked to/from nittygriddy.com web site or incorporated herein, and takes no responsibility therefore. All such information is provided for convenience purposes only and all users thereof should be guided accordingly.

This web site is believed to provide accurate and authoritative information in regards to the subject matter covered. The accuracy of the information is not guaranteed and is provided with the understanding that I am not rendering medical, psychological, legal, accounting, tax or any other kind of professional service. If expert assistance is required, then the services of a competent, licensed professional should be sought.

**Legal Disclaimer**

nittygriddy.com reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when it believes that disclosure is necessary to protect its rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on nittygriddy.com.

*By using the nittygriddy.com website, you are agreeing to all of these terms, conditions and notices. If you do not agree to any or even some of these conditions, please do not use this site. I reserve the right, at my discretion, to update or revise this disclaimer. I encourage you to periodically check this page for any updates, changes and revisions because your continued use of nittygriddy.com following any changes to these conditions constitutes your acceptance of those changes.

Thank You.

Ingrid Abboud aka Griddy

*For all purposes the terms nittygriddy.com, I, We and Our are one and the same and refer to the owner(s) and/or management of this website. **  
**
